Even if I take a different path, even if there are detours
Nothing will change, will it?
Bystanders lamented, denied me, and repeatedly pushed me away...
And then the seasons went by
With each scenario, one's strong feelings linked everyone together
And now, I shall carry their will: hope for a brighter tomorrow
All those gentle lies become a veil
Beyond it, precious lives are protected
If I cherish everyone's voices, then they'll transcend time
Memories of a summer's day
The memories I've left behind, in the corner of my notebook...
Are like daydreams
The future ahead turns into the past, and paints a color I hadn't conjectured
You taught me that, whenever I close my eyes, you're all by my side
And now, the gate of absolute truth gleams with light...
I'm unable to forget, and that's painful
A single tear falls down on the ground
A love, invisible to the eye, watches over me from afar
Memories of a summer's day
I step on the pedals, ride the favorable wind, and press forward on this new path
And if I aim for the sparkling night sky from that day, we will meet again
(And if I aim)
(We will meet again)
I've been searching for my own world line
Where, just like here, my wonderful friends are shining bright
All those gentle lies become a veil
Beyond it, precious lives are protected
If I cherish everyone's voices, then they'll transcend time
Memories of a summer's day
Toward a grand adventure...