Lying thick on the asphalt
Enveloped by light
Here's the familiar scenery you always walk through
And that's sufficient to make me suffocate
When we get too close, we lose sight of things
My thoughts, yet again, are making my head spin
No words could convey the whole of it—that your existence is irreplaceable
No matter how trivial these moments may feel
What's important is that we spent them together
Now and forever, I want to always be by your side
And you too, who's laughing so innocently
Will someday go far away
Because no one can stop the march of time
I want to keep embracing you, again and again
This world, where we met,
Is merely an ephemeral, brittle hologram
But it shall become a paradise filled with love
If only you'd stay
If only you'd stay with me